So, not sure what's going on, but
somebody just smashed our mailbox at the
Jesus house. How can you hit your
mailbox at the Jesus house?
>> Came to say took out the mailbox. Trash
can is all the way over there.
>> Trash can is trashed. Oh my goodness. He
hit it going that way.
So, he had to cross two lanes of traffic
to do that.
>> Here is tire marks right here, right?
>> This is almost intentional.
>> But we didn't know what it was.
>> It was a little black Honda.
>> Yeah.
>> It was a little black Honda?
>> You think this was intentional?
>> Well,
>> that'd have to be pretty horrible
driving.
>> Blacked out behind the wheel, went
head-on into a guardrail,
ended up in our [__] river. I mean,
>> Yeah, but he didn't black out. He just
kept going. Like I get it, stuff
happens, but having the mailbox smashed
at a Jesus themed Airbnb on 6 6 26 is
just a little bit anomalous to me. What
do you think?